I lied when to stand up and ID number
eleven was needing to come out which is
a fashion app a little ironic copy for
me I know but that's why because I'm not
the best at fashion I would love to have
a wardrobe it had like 15 pieces that I
loved that they were comfortable on me
that they looked good on me they were
interred in true useable like between
them that I had a different outfit for
when I wanted to get a little more
dressed up or I wanted to be a little
more businesslike and mostly so that I'm
just comfortable and look okay so when I
see a cute person out there I can be
like oh yeah I don't feel like I maybe
should have gotten put a more effort
into it and I think together like those
people who love fashion and hopefully in
a non catty way would be would want to
do that for other people I'll be like
yeah love to be able to to dress someone
to be able to say okay here is that 15
pieces in a classic wardrobe and then
you can add these eclectic pieces to
make it your own and we can both buy
them together say okay well we need this
many black yoga pants
it's Vancouver that's just a staple I
mean you need yoga pants you can't go
into house let yoga parents and so with
the other ones the product outs and sup
they're out there what's a little a
circle way but like four more so we
probably make our own gonna make a
thousand pairs of yoga pants how cute
can we make them we're actually making
them you get together on sewing machines
one person get together not one person
maybe a thousand ten people get together
make it Alice and get paid for their
time or get theirs for free whatever it
works out to be but having an app that
allows me to maintain my wardrobe in a
way that's like yes I would like that
outfit to look good on me would it look
good on my body type as unable to give
feedback on the articles of clothing
that I have oh I don't like that it can
choose my my armpit I don't like that it
makes I feel it makes me look
unflattering it's not collaborating to
me for whatever reason they look at that
feedback and everyone else is maybe
people with my exact same body type I'll
have the same thing and we can a
different cut looks better on us maybe
people with my body type obviously love
it in other ways and that's great I mean
you can together our feedback can be
used to make better products we can also
crowd by so that things are cheaper but
still made ethically and last long
there's not paying 20 bucks so it goes
out of fashion we can together decide
what fashion is and again not when it's
100 people we've got a sided fashion is
dragon hoodies everyone's wearing dragon
abhi
I love that world but that's probably
not happening but in a world where we
can say everyone gets to wear what they
want you want to work unicorn onesie is
to your board meeting awesome you're
allowed because we've decided that it's
more important to be an individual that
to be in fashion and fashion is weird to
say that something's in one ear and out
the other and fast fashion and the
disposable nosov it of the people
involved it's a problem and so people
talk about that but but different level
how could a clothing app that just
solves my wardrobe dilemma of like what
do I wear could even be like literally
what do I wear that I own because I've
taken pictures of everything and it's in
there and someone can be like wear this
with this you look good with this well
you don't have that if you could buy it
with other people put it in like oh yeah
this is the third time I should have had
black boots you can even borrow it from
your neighbors and someone's like hey I
have a pair of size six black boots you
want to wear them for the day I don't
know if you want to share shoes it's
usually probably not something I've ever
fun wearing tomorrow but but but sharing
clothes but more importantly being like
oh there's that staple piece that I
don't have can I get in on the next
group 5 or does someone else have a pair
that they don't use that they can give
you and create a more ethical fashion
system that helps every individual user
feel empowered and beautiful or
attractive so people don't want to feel
beautiful strong whatever your fashion
would do an individual scare other
people and helps maintain yeah
everything oh one one apps all their
clothing problems
so that's ID number 11 is a app that
helps me use the knowledge of the crowd
to dress myself and maintain a
minimalist wardrobe